

## Khen Muhammad Cahyo

**Phone Number:** 08813102165

Email: khencahyo02@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Khen Muhammad Cahyo

### **About Me**

I'm Khen Muhammad Cahyo, fresh graduate from State Polytechnic of Malang in study programs DII Software Development on Information Technology Departement. Now, I also have study in DIV Informatics Engineering. I have knowledge about web app and mobile app development with more than 2 years experience and until now I still learn and interest in this field. In addition, im also have interested in Machine Learning field. I'm a person who have a high interest in learning and have a good communication skill in teamwork.

### **Educations**

- DII Software Development in State Poltytecnic of Malang (2022 2024)
- DIV Informatics Engineering in State Polytecnic of Malang (2024 now)

### **Experiences**

### Fullstack Developer in Sekawan Media (Internship)

February 2023 – November 2023

- Lead and conducted Fullstack and Frontend Development workshop on SMKN 6
  Malang.
- Create learning modules (Fullstack Laravel, Frontend ReactJS, Backend Laravel, and Mobile App Ionic).
- Fullstack Developer in the development of Talentnesia Animation LMS web app.

## Research and Development Engineer in Sekawan Media (Contract)

November 2023 – August 2024

I'm as Fullstack Developer, System Analyst, and Engineer Lead in RnD team. Here each jobs that I have in this position.

- Lead the development app in technical field.
- Created a clear blueprints for Human Resources Information System app.
- Develop internal libraries to improve the efficiency of app development.
- Fullstack and Mobile Developer in Human Resources Information System app.
- Fullstack Developer in Audit client app.

## Fullstack Developer Teacher in Sekawan Media (Freelance)

August 2024 – November 2024

• Fullstack Laravel Developer Teacher on SMK Telkom Malang in TEFA programs owned by Sekawan Media.

## Frontend Developer in Sekawan Media (Freelance)

September 2024 – November 2024

• Frontend Developer in Audit BNPT Simawas web app.

## Fullstack Engineer in PT. Beemata Indonesia (Contract)

September 2024 – current

### **License and Certification**

- BNPT Junior Web Developer
- BNPT Junior Instructor
- 1st place UI/UX Challenge PlayIT 2024 in State Polytechnic of Malang

# **Skills**

- Typescript (Intermediate)
- React JS (Intermediate)
- React Native (Intermediate)
- NestJS (Intermediate)
- Laravel (Intermediate)
- Codeigniter (Intermediate)
- UML Diagram (Intermediate)

## Languages

- Indonesia (Native)
- English (Beginner)